The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature and although it may not be suitable
for all viewers, it is for the glory of God .
A young boy slowly limbs into The SCOAN,
supported by a pair of crutches as can be clearly seen.
He cannot put any weight whatsoever onto his left leg.
The placard he is holding reveals why.
After sustaining an injury, a cancerous wound erupted on his leg.
The medical report reveals he has undergone two operations without success.
A closer look at the leg exposes the seriousness of the situation.
The broken bone is actually protruding out of his leg,
and a flow of cancerous fluid is coming from the wound.
This situation has obviously gone beyond the power of nature.
It has become a curse.
Who can remove a curse but God?
My name is Maria Oladiran from Cross River State, Nigeria.
The boy beside me is my son.
His name is David Oladiran.
What is the reason for you being here with your son today?
He had an accident in school while playing karate with a certain boy who hit him and he fell down.
After four days, he told us that he had a problem with his leg.
We took him to the hospital where they treated him and put bandages on him.
But after two days, the leg started swelling and after three weeks, it started opening.
Then the bone came out broken by the side and the doctor said it's a leg cancer and broken bone.
So your son now has leg cancer and a broken bone due to that injury?
Yes.
We can also see that he is using crutches.
Yes because he cannot walk, do anything or go to school.
You mean without these crutches he cannot walk?
He cannot walk.
How has that affected his life?
It is affecting his education and he cannot play with his friends because he sits in one place.
I am the one that is taking care of him everyday.
What did the doctor say about his situation? Is there no solution?
They said there is no solution.
Now you are here with your son at The SCOAN, what do you believe God Almighty will do for him?
I believe that God will heal him and see us through.
Amen! We believe with you that God Almighty will heal your son, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
My name is David Oladiran and I am ten years old.
I have leg cancer and broken bone.
Now you're here at The SCOAN, what do you believe that God will do for you?
I believe that God will heal me.
Amen! We believe with you that God Almighty will heal you, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
HEALING TIME
I would like to see many challenges, sicknesses, diseases and unyielding situations yield to prayer;
I want to see them yield to prayer.
The Lord said, "Okay, if that is your desire for your people and nation,
you do not want to see people sick and you want to see the sick healed
and many infirmities being cured" -
as a result of that demand, the Lord gave us this and today is the first day.
Man of God, please help me! My son's bone is out.
They played karate in the school.
Man of God, please help me, he cannot walk.
Man of God, please help me, my bone is outside.
I cannot walk.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
In the name of Jesus, you are healed.
You are healed indeed, in Jesus' name.
In the name of Jesus, rise up and walk!
Thank You, Jesus Christ! The evidence of God's miracles is our rising and walking.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Master David places his weight on his left leg
and begins to walk without the aid of the crutches for the very first time since the injury.
Glory be to God!
TESTIMONY TIME
Our Father who art in Heaven
Hallowed by Thy name
Thy Kingdom come
Thy will be done on earth as it is in Heaven
Give us this day our daily bread
And forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those who trespass against us
And lead us not into temptation
but deliver us from evil
For Thine is the Kingdom and the power, and the glory, for ever and ever
We're singing, Amen.
Mrs Maria actually kept the bone which once protruded from her son's leg,
serving as undeniable evidence of the miraculous power of God.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
The SCOAN Sunday Service
David Oladiran & Family
Healed Of Leg Cancer & A Broken Bone
The SCOAN Sunday Service
David Oladiran's Leg Bone
Before and After
This is the bone you are looking at.
The Lord is reliable.
Put your trust in Him.
Before and After
David Oladiran & Family
Healed Of Leg Cancer & A Broken Bone
The SCOAN Sunday Service
People of God, praise the Lord!
Emmanuel!
(God with Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Maria Oladiran.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was leg cancer of my son.
This happened when I was in Abuja.
We went to the hospital and they said they would amputate my son's leg.
So, my brother came to our house to greet us and he saw me crying.
He asked me if I had heard of Emmanuel TV and I said no.
Then I began to watch Emmanuel TV.
Listen to that language! They wanted to amputate the leg.
The thought of, 'If they amputate my son's leg, he would remain with one leg'.
You know our mothers are so caring.
The thought of, 'Oh, my child will have only one leg!'
She was thinking about that before her brother came to the house.
She was told to watch Emmanuel TV, and after that she came here.
She was not even here to stop the amputation,
but to stop the pain so that the operation would be successful.
That was the reason why they came.
There is a warehouse you don't know about.
Your head has extra head.
Your leg has extra leg.
Oh my God!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Look!
When you have a vehicle, you have spare parts such as tire, and all others.
You must have at least two each.
Just like we have president and vice president.
That is God for you.
We have gone astray. That is the problem we are facing.
If this hand is injured and is about to be cut, ask God for the extra one.
He would open the warehouse and give it to you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That is exactly what happened. The extra leg is the one God has given to this boy.
That is God for you.
Every part of our body has extra and is being kept in the warehouse.
It depends on your relationship with God.
You can only get this by dynamic faith.
Lack of dynamic faith limits what God can do through us.
Tell your neighbour, "Lack of dynamic faith limits what God can do through us".
Little faith - pain! The next thing is that you have gone too far.
So, this boy would have had just one leg today.
Okay, let's hear from them.
That day was the day that the Morning Water came out.
They placed us on the prayer line.
That was how the man of God walked up to me and I cried, "Man of God, please help me!"
Then he walked to my side and gave me the Morning Water.
I ministered it to my son's leg and that was how it started shaking.
The man of God said that the bone would be replaced and that one would decay.
So, that was how the bone fell out
and now, I give God the glory; my son can go to school. He can play with his friends.
He can do anything on his own now.
Before and After
Emmanuel
(God with Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is David Oladiran.
I am from Oyo State, Nigeria.
I reside in my mother's village in Cross River State.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was leg cancer.
I could not walk, go to school or do anything.
My mum was the person who used to assist me
and I was using crutches to walk.
We went from hospital to hospital and the doctors said that there was no solution
and that they should cut off the leg.
My mum's brother said that we should go to The SCOAN.
Then we came to The SCOAN and were placed on the prayer line.
Then Prophet T.B. Joshua gave my mother the Morning Water.
Thank you. Like I have said, I want to meet you people and to tell you about this boy -
why this miraculous thing happened.
The boy you are seeing is the crown of the house.
They should go and wait for me.
You want to play football inside the church?
Amen! Thank you.
Hallelujah.
David Oladiran & Family
Healed Of Leg Cancer & A Broken Bone
Attention All Emmanuel TV Viewers!
Are you an Emmanuel TV viewer living in Europe, Asia, North or South America, Australia or Africa?
Are you called to join us in changing lives, nations, and the world by becoming an Emmanuel TV partner?
Join us for a special meeting with the Emmanuel TV team sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua
with the New Morning Water at the following locations:
Birmingham, UK, Saturday the 27th of January 2018;
Paris, France, Saturday the 10th of February 2018.
Watch out for more information coming soon.
For UK, contact: +44 798 503 4222
Email: uk@emmanuel.tv
For France, contact: +33 142 888 047
Email: fr@emmanuel.tv
"The beauty of life does not depend on how happy you are,
but on how happy others can be because of you." - T.B. Joshua